Finding Aid for Bureau of School Services (University of Michigan) Records 1871-1992
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Accreditation Inspection Reports 1871-1992
  - H-L
    - Highland
      - Highland Milford High School 1986-1992 (Box 76)
        (see also Milford)
    - Highland Park
      - Highland Park (Community) High School
        - 1926-1986 (Box 76)
        - 1986-1992 (Box 77)
      - St. Benedict High School 1925-1966 (Box 77)
    - Hillman
      - Hillman (Junior/Senior) High School 1926-1992 (Box 77)
    - Hillsdale
      - Hillsdale High School 1930-1992 (Box 77)
    - Holland
      - Holland Christian High School 1925-1992 (Box 77)
      - Holland High School 1928-1992 (Box 77)
      - Hope College High School (Hope Preparatory School) 1921-1935 (Box 78)
      - St. Augustine Seminary High School 1966-1977 (Box 78)
      - West Ottawa High School 1963-1992 (Box 78)
    - Holly
      - Holly (Senior) High School 1905-1992 (Box 78)
      - Adelphian Academy 1932-1986 (Box 78)
    - Holt
      - Holt High School 1926-1992 (Box 78)
    - Holton
      - Holton (Rural) High School 1926-1992 (Box 79)
    - Homer
      - Homer (Community) High School 1921-1992 (Box 79)
    - Honor
      - Honor (Rural Agricultural) High School 1926-1962 (Box 79)
    - Hopkins
      - Hopkins High School 1921-1992 (Box 79)
    - Horton
      - Hanover-Horton High School 1940-1992 (Box 79)
    - Hougton
      - Houghton High School 1905-1992 (Box 79)
    - Houghton Lake
      - Houghton Lake High School 1929-1992 (Box 80)
    - Howard
      - Tri County City High School (Howard City High School) 1906-1992 (Box 80)
    - Howell
      - Howell High School 1905-1992 (Box 80)
    - Hudson
      - Hudson High School 1905-1992 (Box 80)
      - Sacred Hearth High School 1932-1944 (Box 80)
    - Hudsonville
      - Hudsonville High School 1924-1992 (Box 80)
      - Unity Christian High School 1954-1992 (Box 81)
    - Hulbert
      - Hulbert High School 1940 (Box 81)
    - Ida
      - Ida (Rural Agricultural) High School 1929-1991 (Box 81)
    - Imlay City
      - Imlay City (Junior/Senior) High School 1913-1992 (Box 81)
    - Indian River
      - Inland Lakes High School 1955-1992 (Box 81)
    - Inkster
      - Cherry Hill High School 1962-1986 (Box 81)
      - Huron Valley Lutheran 1978 (Box 81)
      - Inkster High School
        - 1934-1986 (Box 81)
        - 1986-1992 (Box 82)
      - Peterson Warren Academy 1978-1981 (Box 82)
      - (F.D.) Roosevelt High School 1949-1957 (Box 82)
    - Interlochen
      - Interlochen Arts Academy 1965-1992 (Box 82)
    - Ionia
      - Ionia High School 1905-1992 (Box 82)
      - SS. Peter and Paul High School 1925-1961 (Box 82)
    - Iron Mountain
      - Iron Mountain Senior High School 1905-1992 (Box 82)
      - Felch (Township) High School (became North Dickinson High School) 1926-1970 (Box 82)
      - North Dickinson High School (formerly Felch High School) 1972-1992 (Box 83)
    - Iron River
      - West Iron County High School (formerly Iron River High School) 1907-1992 (Box 83)
    - Ironwood
      - Ironwood Catholic High School (formerly St. Ambrose Catholic High School) 1913-1984 (Box 83)
      - Roosevelt School 1952-1954 (Box 83)
      - (Luther L.) Wright High School (formerly Ironwood High School) 1905-1992 (Box 83)
    - Island Lake
      - Michigan Military Academy 1917-1923 (Box 83)
    - Ishpeming
      - Champion High School/National Mine High School (Nice Community Schools) 1970-1974 (Box 83)
        (see also National Mine)
      - Ishpeming High School 1905-1992 (Box 83)
      - Westwood High School 1975-1992 (Box 83)
    - Ithaca (Box 84)
      - Ithaca High School 1908-1992 (Box 84)
    - Jackson
      - East Jackson High School 1929-1991 (Box 84)
      - Jackson High School 1938-1992 (Box 84)
      - Lumen Christi High School 1969-1992 (Box 84)
      - Northwest High School 1959-1992 (Box 84)
      - Parkside High School 1963-1981 (Box 84)
      - St. John High School 1918-1967 (Box 85)
      - St. Mary High School 1915-1967 (Box 85)
      - Vandercook Lake High School 1929-1992 (Box 85)
      - Woodworth High School 1954 (Box 85)
    - Jenison
      - Jenison Senior High School 1970-1992 (Box 85)
    - Jerome
      - Jerome High School 1929-1930 (Box 85)
    - Johannesburg
      - Lewiston High School (formerly Johannesburg Rural Agricultural School) 1932-1992 (Box 85)
    - Jonesville
      - Jonesville (Community Junior/Senior) High School 1907-1992 (Box 85)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 86)
      - Central High School 1910-1992 (Box 86)
      - Kalamazoo Christian High School 1940-1992 (Box 86)
      - Gull Road School 1949 (Box 86)
      - (Msgr. John R.) Hackett Catholic Central High School 1965-1992 (Box 86)
      - Loy Norrix High School 1960-1992 (Box 86)
      - Oakwood Park Junior High School 1934 (Box 86)
      - (Msgr.) O'Brien High School (formerly St. Augustine High School) 1964-1970 (Box 86)
      - St. Augustine High School (later Msgr. O'Brien High School) 1926-1963 (Box 86)
      - Western State High School (University High School, taken over by WMU) 1914-1965 (Box 86)
    - Kaleva (Box 87)
      - Kaleva (Rural Agricultural) High School 1927-1958 (Box 87)
    - Kalkaska
      - Kalkaska High School 1910-1992 (Box 87)
    - Keego Harbor
      - Roosevelt/Kalkaska/West Bloomfield High School 1929-1955 (Box 87)
    - Kent City
      - Kent City High School 1916-1992 (Box 87)
    - Kentwood
      - East Kentwood High School 1962-1992 (Box 87)
    - Kenton
      - Duncan Township High School 1929-1943 (Box 87)
    - Kinde
      - North Huron High School (formerly Kinde High School) 1921-1992 (Box 87)
    - Kingsford
      - (Edward G.) Kingsford High School 1926-1992 (Box 88)
    - Kingsley
      - Kingsley (Paradise Township Unit) High School 1929-1992 (Box 88)
    - Kingston
      - Kingston (Community) High School 1928-1992 (Box 88)
    - Laingsburg
      - Laingsburg (Community) High School 1921-1992 (Box 88)
    - L'Anse
      - L'Anse High School 1921-1992 (Box 88)
    - Lake City
      - Lake City (Rural Agricultural) High School 1913-1992 (Box 88)
    - Lake Leelanau
      - St. Mary High School 1943-1944 (Box 89)
    - Lake Linden
      - Lake Linden-Hubbel High School 1905-1992 (Box 89)
    - Lake Odessa
      - Lakewood (Lake Odessa) High School 1911-1992 (Box 89)
    - Lake Orion
      - Lake Orion High School (formerly Orion High School) 1912-1992 (Box 89)
    - Lakeview
      - Lakeview (Community) High School 1912-1992 (Box 89)
    - Lambertville
      - Bedford Rural Agricultural High School (formerly Lambertville High School) 1926-1953 (Box 89)
    - L'Anse
      - L'Anse High School 1907-1992 (Box 90)
    - Lansing
      - Catholic Central High School (formerly Msgr. John A. Gabriel High School and O'Rafferty High School) 1963-1992 (Box 90)
      - Central High School 1919-1940 (Box 90)
      - Eastern High School 1929-1992 (Box 90)
      - Everett High School 1936-1992 (Box 90)
      - (Msgr. John A.) Gabriel High School (see Catholic Central High School) (Box 91)
      - Hill Community High School 1976-1981 (Box 91)
      - O'Rafferty High School (see Catholic Central High School) (Box 91)
      - Resurrection High School 1938-1962 (Box 91)
      - St. Mary Cathedral High School 1915-1963 (Box 91)
      - (J.W.) Sexton High School 1946-1992 (Box 91)
      - Waverly High School 1965-1992 (Box 91)
    - Lapeer
      - Lapeer East High School 1976-1985 (Box 91)
      - Lapeer West High School (formerly Lapeer Senior High School) 1905-1992 (Box 91)
    - Lathrup Village
      - Southfield-Lathrup High School 1975-1992 (Box 92)
    - Lauruim
      - Sacred Heart High School 1923-1960 (Box 92)
    - Lawrence
      - Lawrence High School 1921-1992 (Box 92)
    - Lawton
      - Lawton Community High School 1912-1992 (Box 92)
    - Leland
      - Leland (Rural Agricultural) High School 1939-1992 (Box 92)
    - Lenox (Lenox-Richmond)
      - St. Augustine High School 1942-1947 (Box 92)
    - Leroy
      - Leroy (Agricultural) High School (later Pine River High School) 1928-1992 (Box 93)
    - Leslie
      - Leslie High School 1909-1992 (Box 93)
    - Lexington
      - Lexington High School 1926-1944 (Box 93)
    - Lincoln
      - Alcona High School 1955-1992 (Box 93)
    - Lincoln Park
      - Lincoln Park High School 1928-1992 (Box 93)
    - Linden
      - Linden (Community) High School 1921-1992 (Box 93)
    - Litchfield
      - Litchfield High School 1916-1992 (Box 94)
    - Livonia
      - Bentley High School 1951-1984 (Box 94)
      - Clarenceville High School 1953-1992 (Box 94)
      - Franklin High School 1962-1992 (Box 94)
      - Ladywood High School 1954-1992 (Box 94)
      - (Adlai E.) Stevenson High School 1968-1992 (Box 94)
      - Winston Churchill High School 1970-1992 (Box 95)
    - Lowell
      - Lowell (Senior) High School 1906-1992 (Box 95)
    - Ludington
      - Ludington (Senior/Central) High School 1905-1992 (Box 95)
      - St. Simon High School 1921-1967 (Box 95)
    - Luther
      - Luther (Rural Agricultural/Community) High School 1928-1957 (Box 95)
    - Lyons
      - Lyons (Lyons-Muir) High School 1916-1964 (Box 95)
  - M-N
    - Mackinaw City
      - Mackinaw City High School 1926-1961 (Box 95)
    - Mackinac Island
      - Mackinac Island Public Schools 1978-1980 (Box 95)
    - Macon
      - Boysville of Michigan High School 1952-1966 (Box 95)
    - Madison Heights
      - Bishop Foley High School 1969-1992 (Box 96)
      - Lamphere High School 1958-1992 (Box 96)
      - Madison High School 1956-1992 (Box 96)
    - Mancelona
      - Mancelona High School 1905-1992 (Box 96)
    - Manchester
      - Manchester High School 1905-1992 (Box 96)
    - Manistee
      - Catholic Central High School (formerly St. Joseph High School) 1921-1992 (Box 97)
      - Manistee High School 1910-1992 (Box 97)
    - Manistique
      - Manistique High School 1907-1992 (Box 97)
    - Manton
      - Manton (Consolidated/Rural Agricultural) High School 1906-1992 (Box 97)
    - Maple City
      - Glen Lake High School 1961-1992 (Box 97)
    - Maple Grove Township
      - Maple Grove (St. Michael) High School 1934-1938 (Box 97)
    - Maple Rapids
      - Maple Rapids High School 1929-1954 (Box 97)
    - Marcellus
      - Marcellus High School 1910-1992 (Box 98)
    - Marenisco
      - Roosevelt High School (later Marenisco High School?) 1922-1964 (Box 98)
    - Marine City
      - Cardinal Mooney Catholic High School 1986-1992 (Box 98)
      - Holy Cross High School 1927-1989 (Box 98)
      - Ward Cottrell High School (formerly Marine City High School) 1902-1992 (Box 98)
    - Marion
      - Marion High School 1914-1992 (Box 98)
    - Marlette
      - Marlette (Junior/Senior) High School 1906-1992 (Box 99)
    - Marne
      - Berlin High School 1926-1958 (Box 99)
    - Marquette
      - Bishop Baraga Central High School 1922-1969 (Box 99)
      - Marquette (Senior) High School 1905-1992 (Box 99)
      - John D. Pierce High School (formerly Northern Normal High School) 1921-1961 (Box 99)
    - Marshall
      - Marshall High School 1905-1992 (Box 99)
    - Martin
      - Martin (Junior and Senior) High School 1911-1992 (Box 100)
    - Marysville (St. Clair County)
      - Marysville High School 1923-1992 (Box 100)
    - Mason
      - Mason High School 1905-1992 (Box 100)
    - Mass
      - Mass High School (formerly Greenland Township High School) 1911-1967 (Box 100)
    - Mattawon
      - Mattawon High School 1918-1992 (Box 100)
    - Mayville
      - Mayville (Community) High School 1915-1992 (Box 101)
    - McBain
      - McBain Rural Agricultural School 1916-1992 (Box 101)
    - McBrides
      - McBrides High School 1929-1938 (Box 101)
    - McMillan
      - Columbus Township Rural Agricultural High School 1935-1947 (Box 101)
    - Mecosta
      - Mecosta (Rural Agricultural/Consolidated) High School (Box 101)
    - Melvindale
      - Melvindale High School 1928-1991 (Box 101)
    - Memphis
      - Memphis High School
        - 1917-1985 (Box 101)
        - 1986-1992 (Box 102)
    - Mendon
      - Mendon High School 1908-1992 (Box 102)
    - Menominee
      - Menominee (Area) High School 1905-1992 (Box 102)
      - Michigan Military Academy 1930 (Box 102)
      - Upper Peninsula School of Agriculture and Home Economics (also known as Upper Peninsula Agricultural School) 1928-1952 (Box 102)
    - Merrill
      - Merrill (Community/Public) High School 1937-1992 (Box 102)
      - Sacred Heart High School 1935-1946 (Box 102)
    - Merritt
      - Merritt (Consolidated/Rural Agricultural) High School 1937-1957 (Box 102)
    - Mesick
      - Mesick Consolidated High School (formerly Springville Rural Agricultural High School) 1919-1991 (Box 102)
    - Metamora
      - Metamora High School 1929-1940 (Box 102)
    - Michigamme
      - Michigamme Township High School 1922-1946 (Box 102)
    - Michigan Center
      - Michigan Center High School 1930-1992 (Box 103)
    - Middleton
      - Fulton High School 1966-1992 (Box 103)
        (see also Perrinton)
    - Middleville
      - Thornapple Kellogg High School 1929-1992 (Box 103)
    - Midland
      - Bullock Creek High School 1964-1991 (Box 103)
      - Herbert Henry Dow High School 1970-1992 (Box 103)
      - Midland High School 1925-1992 (Box 104)
      - Regina High School 1965-1971 (Box 104)
    - Milan
      - Milan High School 1905-1992 (Box 104)
    - Milford
      - Milford High School 1906-1985 (Box 104)
        (see also Highland: Highland Milford High School)
      - Lakeland High School 1975-1986 (Box 104)
    - Millersburg
      - Millersburg High School 1929, 1939 (Box 104)
    - Millington
      - Millington (Community) High School 1912-1992 (Box 104)
    - Minden City
      - Minden City Public High School 1943-1947 (Box 105)
    - Mio Au Sable
      - Mio Au Sable High School (formerly Mio Agricultural High School) 1925-1992 (Box 105)
    - Monroe
      - Catholic Central High School 1949-1992 (Box 105)
      - Jefferson High School 1963-1992 (Box 105)
      - Monroe High School 1907-1992 (Box 105)
      - St. Mary Academy 1906-1992 (Box 105)
    - Montague
      - Montague (Township Consolidated) High School 1921-1992 (Box 106)
    - Montgomery
      - Montgomery High School 1925-1948 (Box 106)
    - Montrose
      - Hill-McClay High School (formerly Montrose High School) 1927-1991 (Box 106)
    - Morenci
      - Morenci (Area) High School 1907-1992 (Box 106)
    - Morley
      - Morley-Stanwood High School (formerly Morley Consolidated High School) 1926-1992 (Box 106)
    - Morrice
      - Morrice (Consolidated) High School 1924-1992 (Box 107)
    - Mount Clemens
      - Chippewa Valley High School 1964-1992 (Box 107)
      - Clintondale High School 1959-1992 (Box 107)
      - L'Anse Creuse High School 1958-1992 (Box 107)
      - L'Anse Creuse High School North 1976-1992 (Box 107)
      - Lutheran High School North 1978-1992 (Box 108)
      - Mount Clemens High School 1906-1992 (Box 108)
      - St. Mary High School (later Cardinal Mooney High School) 1917-1985 (Box 108)
      - St. Louis High School 1954-1970 (Box 108)
      - St. Peter's High School 1915-1916 (Box 108)
    - Mt. Morris
      - Elizabeth Ann Johnson Memorial High School (formerly Mt. Morris High School) 1918-1992 (Box 108)
      - St. Mary High School 1929-1970 (Box 108)
    - Mt. Pleasant
      - Beal City High School 1972-1992 (Box 109)
      - Central (Michigan State) Normal High School 1917-1924 (Box 109)
      - Mt. Pleasant High School 1905-1992 (Box 109)
      - Sacred Heart Academy High School 1909-1992 (Box 109)
    - Muir
      - Muir High School 1937-1950 (Box 109)
    - Munising
      - William Mather High School (later Munising High School) 1929-1992 (Box 109)
    - Muskegon
      - Catholic Central 1953-1992 (Box 109)
      - Mona Shore High School 1964-1992 (Box 110)
      - Muskegon High School 1905-1992 (Box 110)
      - Oakridge High School 1966-1992 (Box 110)
      - Orchard View High School 1962-1992 (Box 110)
      - Reeths Puffer High School 1960-1992 (Box 110)
      - St. Jean High School 1928-1952 (Box 110)
      - St. Joseph High School (became Catholic Central High School) 1936-1952 (Box 110)
      - St. Mary's High School (became Catholic Central High School) 1921-1953 (Box 111)
      - Western Michigan Christian High School 1949-1992 (Box 111)
    - Muskegon Heights
      - Muskegon Heights High School 1922-1992 (Box 111)
    - Nahma
      - Nahma High School 1940-1941 (Box 111)
    - Napoleon
      - Napoleon (Rural Agricultural) High School 1925-1992 (Box 111)
    - Nashville
      - Nashville (Kellogg) High School (later Maple Valley High School) 1921-1964 (Box 111)
    - National Mine
      - National Mine High School 1921-1968 (Box 111)
        (see also Ishpeming: Champion High School)
    - Nazareth
      - Nazareth Academy 1914-1963 (Box 111)
    - Negaunee
      - Negaunee High School 1905-1992 (Box 112)
      - St. Paul High School 1936-1967 (Box 112)
    - Newaygo
      - Newaygo High School 1907-1992 (Box 112)
    - New Baltimore
      - Anchor Bay High School 1921-1992 (Box 112)
        (formerly New Baltimore High School)
      - St. Mary High School 1929-1948 (Box 112)
    - Newberry
      - Newberry High School 1907-1992 (Box 112)
    - New Boston
      - Huron High School 1952-1992 (Box 113)
    - New Buffalo
      - New Buffalo (Area) High School 1926-1992 (Box 113)
    - New Era
      - New Era High School 1940 (Box 113)
    - New Haven
      - New Haven High School 1923-1992 (Box 113)
    - New Hudson
      - New Hudson (Consolidated/Rural Agricultural) High School 1926-1947 (Box 113)
    - New Lothrop
      - New Lothrop High School 1928-1992 (Box 113)
      - Maple Grove High School 1939-1953 (Box 113)
      - St. Michael High School 1954-1970 (Box 113)
    - New Troy
      - New Troy High School 1922-1965 (Box 114)
    - Niles
      - Brandywine High School 1962-1992 (Box 114)
      - Niles Senior High School 1927-1992 (Box 114)
    - North Adams
      - North Adams (North Adams-Jerome) (Rural Agricultural) High School 1909-1989 (Box 114)
    - North Branch
      - North Branch (Area) High School 1913-1991 (Box 114)
    - North Muskegon
      - North Muskegon High School 1934-1992 (Box 115)
    - Northport
      - Northport (Rural Agricultural) High School 1950-1992 (Box 115)
    - Northville
      - Northville High School 1915-1992 (Box 115)
    - Norway
      - Norway High School 1907-1992 (Box 115)
    - Novi
      - Novi High School 1968-1992 (Box 115)
  - O-Q
    - Oak Park
      - Oak Park High School 1957-1992 (Box 116)
    - Okemos
      - Okemos (Consolidated) High School 1923-1992 (Box 116)
    - Olivet
      - Olivet (Community) High School (formerly Walton Township Unit High School) 1935-1992 (Box 116)
    - Omer
      - Omer High School 1940-1942 (Box 116)
    - Onaway
      - Onaway (Area Community) High School 1916-1991 (Box 116)
    - Onekama
      - Onekama Consolidated High School 1930-1991 (Box 117)
    - Onsted
      - Onsted Community High School 1917-1992 (Box 117)
    - Ontonagon
      - Ontonagon (Area Junior/Senior) High School 1907-1992 (Box 117)
    - Orchard Lake
      - St. Mary's Preparatory School (St. Cyrillus and Methodius Seminary High School) 1915-1992 (Box 117)
      - West Bloomfield High School 1957-1979 (Box 117)
    - Ortonville
      - Brandon High School (formerly Ortonville High School) 1918-1992 (Box 118)
    - Oscoda
      - Oscoda Area High School 1921-1992 (Box 118)
    - Osseo
      - Osseo High School 1927-1943 (Box 118)
    - Otisville
      - LakeVille Memorial High School (formerly Otisville High School) 1923-1992 (Box 118)
    - Otsego
      - Otsego High School 1907-1992 (Box 118)
    - Ottawa Lake
      - Whiteford High School 1954-1992 (Box 119)
    - Otter Lake
      - Otter Lake High School 1931-1937 (Box 119)
    - Ovid
      - Ovid High School 1905-1965 (Box 119)
    - Owendale
      - Owendale-Gagetown High School (formerly Owendale High School; includes Brookfield Township High School) 1930-1992 (Box 119)
    - Owosso
      - Bible Holiness Seminary High School (Owosso Bible College High School) 1928-1953 (Box 119)
      - Owosso High School 1905-1992 (Box 119)
      - St. Paul High School 1928-1970 (Box 119)
      - Springvale Academy 1947-1971 (Box 119)
    - Oxford
      - Dominican Academy 1968-1969 (Box 120)
      - Oxford (Area Community) High School 1905-1991 (Box 120)
    - Painesdale
      - Jeffers High School (formerly Painesdale [Adams Township] High School) 1915-1983 (Box 120)
    - Palmer
      - Palmer (Richmond Township) High School 1928-1940 (Box 120)
    - Parchment
      - Parchment High School 1960-1992 (Box 120)
    - Parma
      - Western High School (formerly Parma Union High School) 1928-1992 (Box 120)
    - Paw Paw
      - Paw Paw High School 1906-1992 (Box 120)
    - Peck
      - Peck (Community) High School 1929-1991 (Box 121)
    - Pelkie
      - Pelkie High School 1930 (Box 121)
    - Pellston
      - Pellston High School (formerly McKinley Township Agricultural High School) 1915-1992 (Box 121)
    - Pentwater
      - Pentwater High School 1916-1991 (Box 121)
    - Pequaming
      - Pequaming High School 1937-1942 (Box 121)
    - Perrinton
      - Middleton-Fulton Township High School 1929-1965 (Box 121)
    - Perry
      - Perry High School 1919-1992 (Box 121)
    - Petersburg
      - Summerfield High School 1915-1991 (Box 122)
    - Petoskey
      - Petoskey High School 1905-1992 (Box 122)
      - St. Francis Xavier High School 1953-1970 (Box 122)
    - Pewamo
      - Pewamo-Westphalia High School (Pewamo Rural Agricultural High School) 1942-1991 (Box 122)
    - Pickford
      - Pickford (Township) High School 1923-1965 (Box 122)
    - Pigeon
      - Laker High School (formerly Elkton-Pigeon-Bay Port High School) 1920-1992 (Box 122)
    - Pinckney
      - Pinckney High School 1916-1992 (Box 123)
    - Pinconning
      - Pinconning (Area/Community) High School 1921-1992 (Box 123)
      - St. Michael High School 1932-1966 (Box 123)
    - Pittsford
      - Pittsford (Area/Rural Agricultural) High School 1923-1992 (Box 123)
    - Plainwell
      - Plainwell High School 1905-1992 (Box 123)
    - Plymouth
      - Bentley High School (see Livonia) (Box 124)
      - Plymouth Centennial Educational Park (formerly Plymouth High School-includes Plymouth-Salem and Plymouth Canton high schools) 1905, 1954-1980 (Box 124)
        (see also Canton)
      - Plymouth Christian Academy 1988-1992 (Box 124)
        (see also Canton: Plymouth Centennial Educational Park)
      - Plymouth High School 1906-1951 (Box 124)
        (see also Plymouth Centennial Educational Park)
    - Pontiac
      - Emmanuel Christian High School 1956-1959 (Box 124)
      - Lambert School 1954-1955 (Box 124)
      - Lincoln Junior High School 1953 (Box 124)
      - Pontiac Catholic High School 1968-1992 (Box 124)
      - Pontiac Central High School 1906-1992 (Box 124)
      - Pontiac Northern Senior High School 1947-1992 (Box 124)
      - St. Frederick High School 1925-1967 (Box 124)
      - St. Michael High School 1956-1967 (Box 124)
      - Waterford Mott High School 1971-1992 (Box 124)
      - Waterford Township High School 1949-1983 (Box 125)
    - Portage
      - Portage Agricultural High School 1924-1939 (Box 125)
      - Portage Central High School 1965-1992 (Box 125)
      - Portage Northern High School 1966-1992 (Box 125)
      - Portage Township High School 1948-1959 (Box 125)
    - Port Austin
      - Port Austin High School 1927-1962 (Box 125)
    - Port Hope
      - Port Hope High School 1928-1943 (Box 125)
    - Port Huron
      - Fort Gratiot Township School 1940-1950 (Box 125)
      - Port Huron Catholic High School 1965-1971 (Box 125)
      - Port Huron Central High School 1972-1980 (Box 125)
      - Port Huron High School 1905-1992 (Box 125)
      - Port Huron Northern High School 1965-1992 (Box 126)